[{"answer": "Well, the situation is pretty tense.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 24, "question": "What's going on in Benghazi right now?", "qSentId": 23}, {"answer": "Actually, at the moment it's gone relatively quiet.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Are they still out in Tahrir Square?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "The United States issued a travel warning just last month talking about the increase in political violence, assassinations, car bombings, warned that the wide array of militias could begin engaging with each other at any time, at anyplace in the country and cautioned Americans to stay away from Libya and particularly certain parts of Libya.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 96, "question": "Do you think there were some warning signals missed that could have prevented what happened in Benghazi?", "qSentId": 95}, {"answer": "I think he would say waver not, do not fear the future.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "If he were alive now, what would he want the U.S. to do in the short term as a result of what happened in Libya this week?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Given the circumstances in Benghazi, Wolf, probably not -- probably because there had been similar attacks on the British ambassador's convoy, there had been an infiltration of Islamic extremists from the southern part of Libya, there had been a series of attacks near the airport.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Was this consulate adequately protected?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Well, with respect to Libya, I don't think it has to do with hatred of the United States.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Was it simply that anti-Islamic film or is there something much bigger here that explains this hatred of the United States?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "I think he's trying to do the best he can under the circumstances.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "How do you think President Obama is handling this crisis?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "We were absolutely caught by surprise.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 167, "question": "When you heard about the killing of the U.S. ambassador and three other Americans, what went through your mind?", "qSentId": 166}, {"answer": "We believe that because we have a successful revolution to overthrow the brutal regime, the former regime, the element of Gadhafi former regime, who are financed by outside of Libya, financing them inside the country.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Who do you believe, Your Highness, was responsible for these murders?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "These are Gadhafi -- these are Gadhafi you can say sympathizers and supporters who have taken -- who have control of Libyan funds overseas.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "Who is financing these elements according to your information?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "We do -- the prime -- the elected prime minister yesterday announced the capture and the arrest of four members of those -- of those criminals.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Is there a connection between al Qaeda and whom you believe to be responsible for these murders?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "I believe that strongly that they're doing this for, one, the 9/11, two, to disrupt the Libyan-American relationship; three is to undermine the successful revolution because yesterday Libya elected the prime minister who is a capable, able, U.S.-educated, and we are proud to have him to be our prime minister to lead our country forward.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "I do not, but my family members do.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "Did you know Ambassador Stevens personally?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "Frankly, Wolf, they don't have much, but they have money and they have resources that they employ to Libyans who are right now seeking to -- for stability.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "How much influence do these elements still have inside Libya?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Sure, absolutely, Wolf.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Do you want to respond to that?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I think even Mitt Romney has suggested that within a certain time frame, maybe he might not have said it that way.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "Margaret, I don't want to rehash too much history, but was that a blunder?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I think you're more likely to see Mitt Romney do it than President Obama, because that kind of clarity is a luxury that you have -- that candidate Obama had in 2008 when you're not president of the United States.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "And the second part of the question, Ben, would it be smart for Mitt Romney to deliver a major foreign policy address?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "Look, I think if you ask any Republican right now, if the election were held today, who would win, most Republicans would say unfortunately it looks like President Obama is leading.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 260, "question": "How worried should these Republicans be?", "qSentId": 259}, {"answer": "It could potentially be very significant, Wolf.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "How significant is that in Ohio, in Florida, in Virginia and some of these other battleground states?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "I think at some point last month this whole presidential campaign degenerated into the two sides calling each other liars, in part over specific things like Paul Ryan's marathon time that maybe were a little bit fudged, but mostly over policy disagreements, where rather than argue the policy, it's more effective in the focus group to call each other names.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "What did you make of that, Ben?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I do, Wolf.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "Are you confident he has got what it takes to beat him in these three debates?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "I don't think that's quite the right way to think about it, Wolf.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "I think it is more sinister.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 351, "question": "Some have suggested that there may be an inspiration from at least some elements of al Qaeda?", "qSentId": 350}, {"answer": "I think Putin has his own concern, which is he has a great deal of Islamic radicalism within his country.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "Is that fear overblown?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I think it fundamentally misunderstand what is happening.", "docId": "120914pmt", "aSentId": 378, "question": "What do you think of that criticism?", "qSentId": 377}]